["Love Mate" Production
Presentation]
Okay, let's move on
to the last couple
They're the hottest
couple these days
Please introduce
yourself
Hello
We're Lee Hyesung
and Shin Yoo-il
I have a question
for Actor Lee Hyesung
You two have been
the talk of the town
since you announced
your relationship
I'd like to ask
how you two first met
["Love Mate"]
Oh, okay…
Well, we're…
Uh…
How did you first meet
Actor Shin Yoo-il?
Ah… I…
We just…
Are you having
trouble answering?
We met at a shooting set
I was working part-time
as an assistant
and Yoo-il came
talked to me first
Wait a minute
You said you met him
through your friend
last time, didn't you?
Or maybe
each of you have
different memories?
No, that's…
That's correct
It was a friend
who let us meet
I fell in love with him
at first sight
and asked my friend
to hook me up
Even after dating
we often worked
as an actor and a staff
Then we finally
got caught
I'd like to say thank you
to my friend
who helped me